<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KId Story</string>
    <string name="button_text">Next</string>

    <string name="text_view">
        Emily is 8 years old. She lives in a big house. She has a huge room. She has many toys and she has a lot of friends. But Emily is not happy. She has a secret.

She doesnt want to tell anyone about her secret. She feels embarrassed. The problem is that if nobody knows about it, there is no one that can help her.

Emily doesnt write her homework. When there is an exam – she gets sick. She doesnt tell anyone, but the truth is she cant read and write. Emily doesnt remember the letters of the alphabet.

One day, Emilys teacher finds out. She sees that Emily cant write on the board. She calls her after class and asks her to tell the truth. Emily says, "It is true. I don't know how to read and write". The teacher listens to her. She wants to help Emily. She tells her, "That's ok. You can read and write if we practice together".

So Emily and her teacher meet every day after class. They practice together. Emily works hard. Now she knows how to read and write!

    </string>

    <string name="text_view1">
        Nicole has a new set of drums. She likes playing the drums. She practices playing the drums all the time.

Her parents tell her, "Nicole, we are happy that you like the drums, but you cant play the drums all the time. There are other people in the apartment. There are other people in the building. There are other people in the neighborhood. And they all want to sleep sometimes!

Nicole listens to them. She says she understands, but she doesnt stop doing it. She practices playing the drums all the time!

Her parents complain, her sister complains, the neighbors complain. Even the cat complains!

"Ok, ok!" Nicole says, "I will be a good girl. I will do it more quietly."

But this doesnt help much. No one can work, no one can rest, and no one can sleep.

One day Nicole comes home and sees her parents and her sister in the living room. She sees new things: a guitar, a trumpet, and a piano. Nicole is very surprised! "Wow!" she says, "What is this?"

"Well," her father answers, "we see that we cant beat you, so we decide to join you!"

    </string>
</resources>